Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records circa 1860–1997 (bulk, 1880–1980) PR 53
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Rolled Drawings, 582 Linear feet in 142 boxes.
  - Virginia
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Plant in plans (Offsite-box RD-090, Tube 296-C)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development (Offsite-box RD-136, Tube 340-B)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Town plans (Offsite-box RD-107, Tube 342-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development | Town plans (Offsite-box RD-137, Tube 342-B)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development (Offsite-box RD-108, Tube 346-A)
    - Virginia—Hampton Roads | Hampton Roads Development (Offsite-box RD-108, Tube 346-B)
    - Virginia—Norfolk | Army & Navy Base (Offsite-box RD-010, Tube 034)
    - Virginia—Norfolk | Army & Navy Base (Offsite-box RD-064, Tube 216)
    - Virginia—Roanoke | Roanoke Hotel (Offsite-box RD-106, Tube 337-A)
    - Virginia—Roanoke | Roanoke Hotel (Offsite-box RD-106, Tube 337-B)
    - Virginia—Roanoke | Roanoke Hotel | Sketches & details (Offsite-box RD-112, Tube 357)
    - Virginia—Virginia Beach | Cavalier Hotel (Offsite-box RD-023, Tube 068)
    - Virginia—Virginia Beach | Cavalier Hotel (Offsite-box RD-033, Tube 107)
    - Virginia—Virginia Beach | Cavalier Hotel (Offsite-box RD-045, Tube 153)
    - Virginia—Virginia Beach | Cavalier Hotel (Offsite-box RD-057, Tube 193)
    - Virginia—Warrington | Doeller | Residence (Offsite-box RD-###, Tube 123)
  - Washington
    - Washington—Seattle | Metropolitan Theatre (Offsite-box RD-010, Tube 033)
    - Washington—Seattle | Olympic Hotel (Offsite-box RD-096, Tube 312-A)
    - Washington—Seattle | Olympic Hotel (Offsite-box RD-096, Tube 312-B)
    - Washington—Seattle | Olympic Hotel (Offsite-box RD-097, Tube 313-A)
    - Washington—Seattle | Olympic Hotel (Offsite-box RD-097, Tube 313-B)
    - Washington—Seattle | Olympic Hotel (Offsite-box RD-097, Tube 314)
  - Wisconsin
    - Wisconsin—Beloit | Eclipse Park (Offsite-box RD-012, Tube 038-A)
    - Wisconsin—Beloit | Eclipse Park (Offsite-box RD-013, Tube 038-B)
    - Wisconsin—Beloit | Eclipse Park (Offsite-box RD-050, Tube 168)
    - Wisconsin—Beloit | Eclipse Park (Offsite-box RD-081, Tube 275)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-123, Tube 385)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-123, Tube 386)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-124, Tube 387)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-124, Tube 388)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-124, Tube 389)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-124, Tube 390)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-125, Tube 391)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-125, Tube 392)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-125, Tube 393)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-125, Tube 394)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-126, Tube 395)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-126, Tube 396)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-126, Tube 397)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-126, Tube 398)
    - Wisconsin—Madison | Wisconsin State Capitol (Offsite-box RD-127, Tube 399)
  - Canada
    - Canada—Montreal | Montreal Stock Exchange (Offsite-box RD-013, Tube 040-B)
    - Canada—Montreal | Montreal Stock Exchange (Offsite-box RD-049, Tube 167-A)
    - Canada—Montreal | Montreal Stock Exchange (Offsite-box RD-049, Tube 167-B)
    - Canada—Toronto | Mount Royal Hotel (Offsite-box RD-019, Tube 057)
    - Canada—Toronto | Mount Royal Hotel (Offsite-box RD-058, Tube 197)
  - Location uncertain
    - Grace, W. R. & Co. | Office Building (Offsite-box RD-134, Tube 304-A)
    - Grace, W. R. & Co. | Office Building (Offsite-box RD-094, Tube 304-B)
    - Loft building, NYC (Offsite-box RD-041, Tube 136)
    - Navarre Hotel | Alterations (Offsite-box RD-061, Tube 203)
    - Niles, O. | Housing development for George A. Fuller Co. (Offsite-box RD-013, Tube 040-A?)
    - Page, Mr. | Voorhees Farm (Alterations to cottage) (Offsite-box RD-086, Tube 290-A)
    - Page, Mr. | Voorhees Farm (Alterations to cottage) (Offsite-box RD-086, Tube 290-B)
    - Page, Mr. | Voorhees Farm (Alterations to cottage) (Offsite-box RD-086, Tube 290-C)
    - Palmer residence (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 083)
    - Presbyterian Church (Offsite-box RD-007, Tube 021-022)
    - Ray, Mary E. Estate | Elevations & sections (Offsite-box RD-014, Tube 044)
    - Roellins | Residence (Offsite-box RD-092, Tube 300)
    - St. Anne's School (Offsite-box RD-002, Tube 003)
    - Salisbury, Mrs. George B. | Cottage & stable (Offsite-box RD-015, Tube 048)
      At least one drawing from this tube is held onsite in the "Residences" drawer in Unit 8A/Bay 40/Drawer 2.
    - Squibb, E. R. | Alteration of Anderson House (Offsite-box RD-026, Tube 082)
    - Stamford House [Hospital?] | Building set of prints (Offsite-box RD-009, Tube 029-A)
    - Stamford House [Hospital?] | Building set of prints (Offsite-box RD-009, Tube 029-B)
    - Vineland [New Jersey?] (Offsite-box RD-055, Tube 187)
- Series II. Flat Files, # Linear feet
  - [2NW, Unit 1B, Case 2, Drawer 14] (Drawer #)
    Scope and Contents
    MATTED DRAWINGS
    St. Nicholas Terrace Elevation
    "Hess Building"
    "N.Y.A.C."
    Prudential Insurance Company
  - [2NW, Unit 1B, Case 2, Drawer 15] (Drawer #)
    Cornelius Vanderbilt II House (5 folders)
    Public, Government, Business Buildings (1 folder)
    National Academy of Design (1 folder)
    New York Produce Exchange (1 folder)
    United States Department of Labor (1 folder)
    Collis P. Huntington Residence
    CCNY-Beaux-Arts
  - [2NW, Unit 7A, Case 20, Drawer 12] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Miscellaneous Buildings
    Folder: Great Hall, College of the City of New York
    Folder: District of Columbia, photos, misc.
    Folder:
    1) Unidentified house or bank
    2) Emigrant Savings Bank
    3) Payne Memorial Gateway
    4) Memorial Arch, Soldiers & Sailors Gateway for Prudential Building, Newark
    5) Gardeners Cottage, Bernardsville
    6) Fountain, Bernardsville
    7) Wisconsin State Capital
    Folder: Churches
    ........Project for St. Paul's Church, [illegible], NJ
    Folder: New York Hospital
    Folder: Department of Justice, Washington, D.C.
    ........Penn Avenue elevation, first floor plan
    Folder: National Academy of Design (1 of 2) (folder says Case E.9 in Print Room)
    Folder: National Academy of Design (2 of 2) (folder says Case E.9 in Print Room)
  - [2NW, Unit 7A, Case 20, Drawer 13] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Residences and Domestic Architecture
    ........Unidentified apartment building
    Folder: Educational Institutions
    ........George Washington University
    ........Unidentified
    ........Western University of Pennsylvania
    Folder: Cleveland Trust Co., 4th Floor plans, basement to 3rd floor
    Folder: Governor Clinton Hotel, blueprints originally in tube 161
    Folder: Project for St. Thomas Church, New York City
    ........5 drawings interior perspectives, façade on 5th Avenue
    Folder: Public Service Corporation, NJ
    ........Municipal Ferries of the city of New York, Brooklyn station
    ........New York Clearing House
  - [2NW, Unit 7A, Case 20, Drawer 14] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Housing Development, Cradock, Va.
    ........Detached houses on Preble Circle; Cradock. VA (2 copies)
    ........Semi-detached houses on Cotton Place; Cradock, VA (2 copies)
    ........Terrace Group of 5 Houses on Ericsson St.; Cradock, VA (2 copies)
    ........Other drawings and views
    Folder: New York Stock Exchange
    Folder: Gallatin National Bank
    Folder: CCNY
  - [2NW, Unit 7A, Case 21, Drawer 4] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Travellers Insurance, Hartford, CT (2 folders)
    Folder: Boys High School, Reading, PA
    Folder: Bank of Pittsburgh
  - [2NW, Unit 7A, Case 21, Drawer 5] (Drawer #)
    1) Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Co.
    2) Proposed Plan, City Hall, Buffalo, NY
    Folder: Montreal Stock Exchange, 2 color renderings
    Folder: Armory, Second Battery [E. 166th St.]
    ........Competition for the Armory, Second Battery
    ........Roof plan, drill hall, dining hall
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 38, Drawer 12] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Misc. Photos
    ........U.S. Post Office, New Haven, CT
    ........New York Post Office
    ........Justice Department, Washington, D.C.
    ........Library of Congress
    ........Buildings for City College of New York
    ........Competition of the Western University of Pennsylvania
    ........George Washington University, general plan
    Folder: Camden County Courthouse competition
    ........9 elevations, sections, plans, rendering of 1st floor plan
    Folder: Montreal Stock Exchange
    ........5 drawings, plans, elevations, sections
    Folder: Prudential Building, Newark, NJ
    ........5 drawings, details, perspectives, 1 additional floor plan
    Folder: 2 schemes of Prudential Building
    Folder: George Post, Misc. Photos
    ........Morris Golf Club, line drawing
    ........"View of sloping levee with municipal wharf house in background," Davenport, IA
    ........Government Bridge, Davenport, IA
    ........View from Antoine Le Claire Park, Davenport, IA
    ........Aerial view of Antoine Le Claire Park, with Dillon Memorial Foundation Davenport, IA
    ........Plan, New Jersey Sanitarium for Tuberculous Diseases, Gardner, NJ
    ........Watercolor of New Jersey Sanitarium for Tuberculous Diseases, Gardner, New Jersey
    ........Drawing of New York City ferry terminals
    ........Ink drawing, "proposed improvements to Long Wharf, Newport, RI
    ........Administration Building, World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago, 1893; Richard M. Hunt, architect
    ........Unidentified building on water, under construction
    ........Drawing of Stamford Hospital, Stamford, CT
    ........Manufacturers and Liberal Arts Building, World's Columbian Exposition, Jackson Park, Chicago (6 copies)
    ........The Liberal Arts Building and a portion of the Court of Honor, World's Columbian Exposition, Chicago, building by Post, peristyle by C.B. Atwood, architect
    ........Unidentified buildings on water (World's Columbian Exposition?)
    ........Portfolio of Photostats of Cleveland Chapter National Town & Country Club, now altered slightly and used by Fenn College
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 38, Drawer 13] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Le Roy Residence, Bernardsville, NJ
    Folder: Ladychapel of the Cathedral of St. Patrick [NYC] 8 elevations, plans, sections
    Folder: Mrs. Vanderbilt's residence, Newport, RI
    Folder: J. Larocque House, Bernardsville, NJ
    Folder: A.C. Train residence, E. 70th St.
    Folder: Houses (misc.)
    Folder: William H. Page Jr., Bernardsville, NJ and house of R.V. Lindabergh
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 38, Drawer 14] (Drawer #)
    Folder: C.C. Bragg residence, Avondale, OH
    Folder: Train, Arthur C., 120 E. 70th St., 2 color renderings
    Folder: United States Post Office, New Haven, CT Elevations, plans, sections
    Folder: Long Island Historical Society, Pierrepont St. elevation
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 38, Drawer 15] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Morris County Golf Club competition, Morristown, NJ
    Folder: Danforth Library Building, Paterson, NJ
    Folder: Hart Memorial Library plans, Troy, NY (2 folders)
    Folder: Free Public Library of Newark, NJ
    ........Color rendering, façade, 7 other drawings
    Folder: Misc. Buildings, folder 2
    ........New York Stock Exchange
    ........Schermerhorn Building, neg. 71950
    ........World Building
    ........Ornamental gate
    ........Coe Building, 636-638 Broadway
    ........Building interior (bank?)
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 1 (2 folders)] (Drawer #)
    Folder 1:
    ........Howard Savings Institution
    ........Office of the Prudential Insurance Co. of America, Newark, NJ
    ........World Building, NY [Pulitzer Building], 2 photos
    ........Park Building, Pittsburgh, 2 photos
    ........Two unidentified photos (Public Service Corporation, Newark, NJ?)
    ........Proposed tower of Prudential Insurance Co.
    ........New York Produce Exchange
    Folder 2:
    ........St. Paul Building
    ........Proposed tower for Prudential Insurance Co., Newark, NJ
    ........Prudential South Building
    ........Mills Building
    ........Union Trust Company, Bronx
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 2: Apartments and Houses (except Huntington) (3 folders)] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Pen and ink drawings of Eclipse Park Development, Beloit, WI
    Folder: Unidentified Residences
    Folder: Apartments: 97th Street, Fenway Hall, Wade Park Apts., Cleveland, OH
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 3: Collis P. Huntington Residence, 5th Avenue and 57th Street (3 folders)] (Drawer #)
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 4: Hotels] (Drawer #)
    Warwick Hotel, NYC 1927-1928
    Folder: Unmarked
    ........Grand Ballroom
    Folder: Hotels (1 of 2)
    ........[Statler Hotel, Buffalo, drawn by "John Vincent?]
    ........Banquet Hall – Statler Hotel [Buffalo]
    ........Proposed Sketch of Hotel; Oswego, NY
    ........Half Moon Hotel; Coney Island
    ........Waldorf Astoria Hotel, 1913
    ........Proposed Hotel; Oswego, NY
    ........Unidentified Hotel
    Folder: Hotels (2 of 2)
    ........Unknown Hotel
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 5: Clubs & Equitable Bldg, Union Trust Co.] (Drawer #)
    Folder M-3 "proposed law"
    ........New Street
    ........Municipal Building
    ........Park Row Building
    ........Flat Iron Building
    ........Wade Park Manor Residential Hotel, Cleveland, OH
    Folder: Clubs 1 of 2
    Folder: Clubs 2 of 2
    Folder: Photos of U.S. Post Office, New Haven, CT
    ........Buildings for CCNY
    ........Competition of the Western University of Penn.
    ........George Washington University—general plan
    Folder: Presentation Drawings
    ........Long Island Historical Society, New York
    ........Troy Savings Bank Building
    ........Metropolitan Opera House?
    ........Union Trust Co.
    ........Equitable Building, NYC, NY
    ........Mutual Life Insurance Building, NYC, NY
    ........New York Hospital
    Folder: Union Club "Old Fogy"
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 6: Commercial Buildings] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Commercial Buildings
    ........Union Trust Co.?
    ........National Building, Akron, OH
    ........Prudential Building, Newark, NJ
    ........Boston Mutual Life Insurance Co. of New York
    ........Post Building, New York
    ........Glens Falls Fire Insurance Co.
    ........Western Life Insurance Building, Milwaukee
    ........Building—Broad and Market Streets, Newark, NJ
    ........Unidentified exchanges
    Folder: Commercial Misc. Buildings 2 of 4, including:
    ........Post Building
    ........Tiffany Building
    ........Equitable Building
    Folder: Commercial Misc. Buildings 3 of 4
    ........Cleveland Trust Co.
    ........Savings Bank New York
    ........Dry Dock Savings Bank
    ........Albany Savings Bank
    Folder: Commercial Misc. Buildings 4 of 4
    ........Unidentified drawing (bad condition)
    Folder: Commercial Buildings—Banks
    ........Montreal Stock Exchange
    ........Williamsburgh Savings Bank
    ........Bank of Pittsburgh
    ........Commercial Union Assurance Company of London
    ........Marine Bank-New York
    ........Unidentified competition drawings
    ........First National Bank, Somerville, NJ
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 7: Commercial, Government and Hospitals] (Drawer #)
    Folder: New York Stock Exchange, including furniture details
    Folder: Government Buildings 1 of 2
    ........Wisconsin State Capitol
    ........Essex County Courthouse
    ........Department of Justice Building, Washington, D.C.
    ........Brooklyn Academy of Music
    Folder: Government Buildings 2 of 2, including U.S. Post Office, Orange, NJ
    Folder: Hospitals
    Folder: New York Hospital Buildings, 11 drawings, elevations, plans, sections
    Folder: U.S. Custom House, 12 competition drawings
    Folder: Department of Justice, Washington, D.C., 4 elevations, sections, including rendering of 1st floor plan
    Folder: Mostly Mt. Sinai Hospital, Cleveland, OH
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 8: Religious Structures, misc.] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Misc.
    ........Unlabeled houses sketch
    ........Unlabeled interior sketch
    Folder: Religious Structures (1 of 3)
    ........Unlabeled church
    ........Grand Plan – Church
    ........Infant School: Transverse Section
    Folder: Religious Structures (2 of 3)
    ........Chapel, West Hampton
    ........Unlabeled church painting
    ........Unlabeled church sketch
    Folder: Religious Structures (3 of 3)
    ........Country church-Side Elevation
    ........Metropolitan Opera House
    ........Unlabeled building
    Folder: Sketches for Building Sculpture: Unidentified
    ........Unlabeled statue
    ........Unlabeled statue (Side Elevation)
    Folder: Competition for Scranton Stn. Misc.
    Folder: Rodef Sholem Synagogue Competition, Pittsburg, PA (7 drawings)
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 9: Colleges & Universities] (Drawer #)
    Folder: City College of New York
    Folder: Library CCNY
    Folder: George Washington University Memorial Hall, etc. (6 plans)
    Folder: Plans for George Washington University
    Folder: Brooklyn Academy of Music
  - [2NW, Unit 8A, Case 40, Drawer 10: Fox Theater & Foreign Material Owned by Post] (Drawer #)
    Folder: Theatre and Office Building for William Fox, 47th and Broadway, New York City
    Folder: Foreign Material
    ........01. Interiors, from book
    ........02. Unlabeled outdoor plan
    ........03. Unlabeled outdoor plan
    ........04. unlabeled outdoor plan
    ........05. Cabinets
    ........06. Cabinets
    ........07. Chairs
    ........08. Chapelle Armenienne
    ........09. Chapelle Armenienne
    ........10. Chapelle Armenienne
    ........11. Hall Interieur, 49 Avenue Victor Hugo
    ........12. Mobelier de Bureau
    ........13. Gromort et Leclerc – Un Theatre Lyrique, 1897
    ........14. Furniture, 1902
    ........15. Unlabeled interiors
    ........16. Furniture of the Modern Style
    ........17. Furniture
    ........18. Furniture of the Modern Style
    ........19. Furniture
    ........20. Furniture of Modern Style
    ........21. Furniture of Modern Style
    ........22. Modern Decorative Art
    ........23. Furniture
    ........24. Furniture
    ........25. Furniture
    ........26. Furniture
    ........27. Furniture
    ........28. Furniture
    ........29. Furniture
    ........30. Furniture
    ........31. Furniture
    ........32. Furniture
    ........33. Furniture
    ........34. Furniture of the Modern Style
    ........35. Modern Decorative Art
    ........36. Furniture of the Modern Style
    ........37. Furniture
    ........38. Furniture
    ........39. Interiors
    ........40. Interiors
    ........41. Furniture of the Modern Style
    ........42. The Architectual Scrapbook
    ........43. Worcester Cathedral – North Side of Nave – Aug 27, 1920
    ........44. Oxford, England columns
    ........45. Oxford, England interiors
    ........46. Oxford, England interiors
    ........47. Winchcombe Church – The South Porch
    ........48. Winchcombe Church – The South Porch
    ........49. Newcastle, England Interior
    ........50. Southwold Church, Suffolk – North Elevation
    ........51. Oddfellows Club Coventry – Warwicks
    ........52. Elgin Cathedral of Scotland
    ........53. Elgin Cathedral of Scotland
    ........54. Elgin Cathedral of Scotland
    ........55. Colonel Gardinier's House, 1720
    ........56. Notre Dame – Lyons, France
    ........57. Pulpit of St. Nicholas of Ghent, Belgium
    ........58. Pulpit of St. Nicholas of Ghent, Belgium
    ........59. Church of San Maurizio of Italy
    ........60. Church of the Immaculata of Genoa, Italy
    ........61. Church of San Bernadino of Verona, Italy
    ........62. The Palazzo Herne of Florence, Italy
    ........63. The Palazzo Herne of Florence, Italy
    ........64. The Palazzo Herne of Florence, Italy
    ........65. The Palazzo Herne of Florence, Italy
    ........66. Palazzo Serra of Genoa, Italy
    ........67. Palazzo Serra of Genoa, Italy
    ........68. Palazzo Doria Tursi of Genoa, Italy
    ........69. Monumente und Stand Bilder Europas
    ........70. Landscape
    ........71. Landscape – Pavillion
    ........72. Building
    ........73. Building
    ........74. Pavillion
    ........75. Pavillion
    ........76. Unlabeled
    ........77. Unlabeled
    ........78. Unlabeled
    ........79. Unlabeled
    ........80. Unlabeled
    ........81. Unlabeled
    ........82. Unlabeled
    ........83. Unlabeled
    ........84. Statue
    ........85. Statue
    Folder: Unlabeled
    ........Le Nouvel Opera de Paris
    ........Unlabeled
    ........City Hall, Brussels
  - [2NW, green shelving, 4.7: City College] (Drawer #)
    City College presentation drawing. Watercolor on very brittle, broken paper, 34.5 x 61.5 inches.
  - [2NW, green shelving, 4.7: New York Stock Exchange] (Drawer #)
    New York Stock Exchange presentation drawing by Hughson Hawley, 1900. Watercolor on paper mounted overall to Masonite, 49.5 x 43.5 inches.
- Series III. Bound Volumes, 1864-1951; 23 Linear feet in 21 boxes.
  Filed alphabetically by format (e.g., cash books, job records, ledgers, etc.) and then chronologically.
  Separated Materials
  Earlier finding aids to this collection included a volume labeled "Payments to Engineers" (1917-1931). On inspection it was discovered to have originated with the architectural firm of McKim, Meade & White, not with George B. Post. It has been placed with the other volumes in that collection (PR-042).
  - Vol. 1. Address book, 1890 May 15 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 2. Bank list & deposits, 1887-1893 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 3. Blueprints. "Eclipse Park Community of Homes…" (reproductions of plans) (Offsite-box 122)
  - Vol. 4. Blueprints. Hospitals (Offsite-box 80)
  - Vol. 5. Blueprints. Hotels [1 of 2] (Offsite-box 81)
  - Vol. 6. Blueprints. Hotels [2 of 2] (Offsite-box 82)
  - Vol. 7. Cash book [cash account], 1877 Apr. 2 - 1887 Jan. 8 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 8. Cash book [private?], 1887 Jan. 1 - 1894 Jan. 2 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 9. Cash book (private), 1894 Jan. 3 - 1901 Jan. 2 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 10. Cash book (private), 1901 Jan. 2 - 1907 Jan. 3 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 11. Cash book, 1887 Jan. 1 - 1895 Sep. 30 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 1)
  - Vol. 12. Cash book, 1895 Sep. 30 - 1905 Jan. 1 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 2)
  - Vol. 13. Cash book, 1904 June 11 - 1905 Oct. 9 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 14. Cash book, 1905 Jan. 3 - June 28 (Offsite-box 75, Folder 3)
  - Vol. 15. Cash book, 1905 Jan. 3 - 1908 Dec. 11 (Offsite-box 70)
  - Vol. 16. Cash book, 1907 Jan. 14 - 1913 Nov. 25 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 17. Cash book, 1909 Jan. 5 - 1914 Aug. 11 (Offsite-box 122)
  - Vol. 18. Cash book, 1914 Sep. 1 - 1919 Dec. 30 (Offsite-box 123)
  - Vol. 19. Cash book, 1920 Jan. 2 - 1923 Mar. 31 (Offsite-box 123)
  - Vol. 20. Cash book, 1923 Apr. 3 - 1926 Apr. 30 (Offsite-box 124)
  - Vol. 21. Cash book, 1926 May 1 - 1929 Nov. 27 (Offsite-box 124)
  - Vol. 22. Cash book, 1929 Dec. 5 - 1942 Apr. 20 (Offsite-box 125)
  - Vol. 23. Cash drawer, 1903 July 1 - 1905 Nov. 29 (Offsite-box 69)
  - Vol. 24. Catalog of architectural drawings supposedly in N-YHS (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 25. Check register, 1894 Jan. 3 - 1904 May 27 (Offsite-box 67)
  - Vol. 26. Contracts, orders, certified bills, 1907-1916 (Offsite-box 72)